Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/snehal-pimple (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

R

Strategic Planning Business Strategy

Certifications

Tableau Essential Training
Python for Data Science and Al

Snehal Pimple

Data Science | Machine Learning | Computer Vision | Data Analyst Boston, Massachusetts, United States

Summary

I have graduated with Master's in Electrical and Computer Engineering at Northeastern University with a concentration in Machine Learning, Computer Vision and Algorithms. I have a professional experience as a Data Scientist and as a Data Analyst. I have build predictive machine learning model and performed data processing and analyzing to provide meaningful insights for clients' products and services.

My interest lies in Data Science, Machine Learning and Analytics.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming Languages: Python, C++, SQL, MATLAB, Java
Data Science Libraries: Numpy, Pandas, Matplotlib, Seaborn, SciKitLearn, TensorFlow, Keras, PyTorch, HDF5
Machine Learning: Ensemble models, Random Forest, Decision tree,

Deep Learning: Backpropagation, Feed-forward, CNN, Seq2Seq, GRU, LSTM, BERT, Attention

Analytical Software and Platform: IBM SPSS, Tableau, Q Research, ASKIA, IBM Dimensions, Advanced MS Excel, PPT

Experience

IKEA

Data Analyst February 2023 - Present (3 months) United States

KNN, SVM, Naive Bayes, K-Means

Willow Innovations, Inc.
Data Science Intern
May 2022 - August 2022 (4 months)
United States

GENESYS Lab - Northeastern University Research Assistant November 2021 - April 2022 (6 months)

Nepa

Data Scientist-Analyst February 2017 - March 2020 (3 years 2 months)

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

Cross-Tab Marketing Services Pvt. Ltd
Data Analyst
September 2014 - January 2017 (2 years 5 months)

Education

Northeastern University

Master's degree, Machine Learning and Computer Vision · (January 2021 - December 2022)

Narsee Monjee Institute of Management Studies
PGDMM, Marketing/Marketing Management, General · (February
2018 - December 2019)

University of Mumbai

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Electronics and Telecommunication · (July 2010 - August 2014)